Hanan Levin

Profile

Hanan Levin, I finished at Be'er Tovia high school and I was in Israel national team in Karate.

Then I joined the army at 18 and became an combat officer at the age of 19, served for 4 Years.

I taught myself a programming language called JavaScript and made small projects.

Employment History

Combat Fitness coach

November 2017 — March 2019

Before the army I'v opened an combat fitness team.

Sargent at Israel defence force

November 2019 — August 2020

Combat officer at Israel defence force

August 2020 — March 2023

Finished at first lieutenant rank.

Education

12 school years, Be'er Tovia high scholl, Be'er Tovia

September 2012 — July 2018

Self taught

I tought myself JavaScript with the help of a lot of hard work, digital courses and friends and family from the high-tech field

Courses

Krav Maga, wingate institute

August 2017 — November 2017

Combat officer rifleman 012, IDF officer leadership academy

August 2020 — February 2021

Deputy company commander

December 2021 — January 2022

Details

Beat Ezra Israel

+972584251120

hananlevingr@gmail.com

Links

Instgram Linkedin

Skills

Ability to Work Under

Pressure

Teamwork

Leadership

Fast learner

Languages

Hebrew

English

Spanish